(Sheldon:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)He will hear it as an attempt
to mend fences,
(Sheldon:)as opposed
to the withering condemnation
(Sheldon:)you and I will know it to be.
(Penny:)Yeah. Yeah, that
was my plan.
(Sheldon:)All right.
Come on. Let's go.
(Sheldon:)Oh, by the way,
thank you
(Sheldon:)for the delicious cocoa.
(Penny:)Oh, you're welcome.
(Sheldon:)Boy, I'm getting
good at this.
(Leonard:)Okay, now that you're
back on the team,
(Leonard:)let's get you caught up.
(Sheldon:)Before you begin,
let me say again
(Sheldon:)how deeply sorry I am
for my earlier behavior
(Sheldon:)and how much I respect
and admire your leadership.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)So as you can see,
(Leonard:)not only can you store
your favorite equations,
(Leonard:)but you can forward them
to your friends
(Leonard:)or post them on Facebook
right from the app.
(Sheldon:)Well, I must say,
I am impressed.
(Leonard:)Thanks.
(Sheldon:)You all have clearly put
in a lot of hard work.